Company

* [About
    
    Vision, values & history](https://www.mojeek.com/about/)
* [Press & Media
    
    Contact, media & assets](https://www.mojeek.com/about/press/)
* [Careers
    
    Join the team](https://www.mojeek.com/about/careers/)
* [Contact Us
    
    Get in touch](https://www.mojeek.com/about/contact)

Products

* [Mojeek Ads
    
    Reach new audiences](https://www.mojeek.com/ads/)
* [Web Search API
    
    Embedded web search](https://www.mojeek.com/services/search/web-search-api/)
* [Site Search API
    
    Embedded site search](https://www.mojeek.com/services/search/site-search-api/)
* [Simple Search Boxes
    
    Extensible search widgets](https://www.mojeek.com/services/search/searchbox.html)

Help & Support

* [Support
    
    Support guides & information](https://www.mojeek.com/support/)
* [Browsers
    
    Browser guides](https://www.mojeek.com/support/browsers/)
* [Mobile
    
    Mobile guides](https://www.mojeek.com/support/smartphones/)
* [API Docs
    
    Developer documentation](https://www.mojeek.com/support/api/)

Engage

* [Blog
    
    Latest updates from us](https://blog.mojeek.com/)
* [Community
    
    Join the discussion](https://community.mojeek.com/)
* [Newsletter
    
    Get updates by email](https://buttondown.email/Mojeek)

* [ ] Search
* [ ] Company
* [ ] Products
* [ ] Help & Support
* [ ] Engage

Privacy Policy
==============

Updated 2nd February 2022. ([view archived versions](https://www.mojeek.com/about/privacy/archive/))

This privacy policy by Mojeek Limited, explains our stance on personal information, in regard to cookies, tracking, logging, data usage, contact information and any links to third parties.

Mojeek follows a strict no tracking privacy policy, and it's quite simple, we don't track our users. In fact, Mojeek was the first ever no tracking/privacy orientated search engine, as can be seen on archive.org and our original privacy policy from when Mojeek was just a side project.

Cookie Policy
-------------

By default and unless specifically agreed to, Mojeek doesn't place any [cookies](http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie) on your computer. If Mojeek does require to place a cookie, your agreement will be requested, for example when setting personal preferences. Also at any time, visiting [this page](https://www.mojeek.com/about/cookie) will list what cookies Mojeek has on your computer, their contents, and an explanation of their values. From that page you can also instruct Mojeek to delete any cookie we have placed.

Tracking and Logging Policy
---------------------------

Mojeek doesn't implement any kind of specific user tracking, whether that be at the time of visit or subsequently via standard logs, which Mojeek does keep indefinitely. These logs contain the time of visit, page requested, possibly referral data, and located in a separate log browser information. IP addresses are not recorded, instead the IP address is replaced with a simple two letter code indicating the visitors country of origin. By doing this, Mojeek removes any possibility of tracking or identifying any particular user. We use a URL parameter to monitor if a campaign landing page visit results in a Mojeek search request. This parameter is visible in the URL and is not used after the first search.

Data Usage
----------

The remaining log data (country, time/date, page requested, referral data, and in a separate log browser data), which although now contains no identifiable data, would still in no situation whatsoever be sold or distributed to any third party vendors. This data is kept private for the sole purpose of storing historical traffic volumes and country demographics of our visitors. We may also use aggregate, non-personal search data to improve our results.

Contact Information
-------------------

We only use your name and email address for the purpose of responding to contact requests that you have made through our Contact page, or for communications regarding registration with the [Mojeek community](https://community.mojeek.com/). We do not use these details for any other purpose. Furthermore, under [GDPR](https://gdpr-info.eu/art-17-gdpr/), we respect that if you request and no longer give consent to us possessing your name and email address for contact reason, we will delete this data.

Other Websites
--------------

The Mojeek website contains links to other websites. This privacy policy only applies to this website. When you proceed to other websites via our links, our privacy policy is void.

Third Parties
-------------

We do not outsource any development of Mojeek to third parties; all development is kept in-house. We pride ourselves on limiting the number of third party products and services that Mojeek consumes.

If you have any further questions please [contact us](https://www.mojeek.com/about/contact), we'll be happy to answer any questions or concerns you may have.

* Search

* Company

* Products

* Help & Support
